As a communicator between the visible and the invisible,
Prophet T.B. Joshua ministers prayer and deliverance in the name of Jesus Christ
to international visitors who have travelled from all over the world
to experience the supernatural move of God in their lives
through God's grace in the life of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Let's watch as the powers of darkness in the life of this young man are exposed.
What is he doing? Do you preach the Gospel?
I was preaching five months ago but I stopped.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come. Come on.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
You possess evil powers.
Yes.
Because right from a small age, the spirit of man entered you.
It's true, Man of God.
Spirit of man.
Yes. It's true.
You don't have women; it's men.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Deliverance takes place as Prophet T.B. Joshua continues to pray for him in Jesus' name.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
He's free.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Later in the Sunday service, during the mass prayer with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
the same young man vomits poisonous substances and he is set free completely in the name of Jesus Christ.
To God be the glory!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Testimony Time
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Marcelo Maldonado Buenos Aires, Argentina
I am 29 years old and I am studying Law in Argentina.
He said that his name is Marcelo. He is from Argentina.
He is 29 years old and he is here to give thanks to God.
Marcelo Maldonado - Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
Last Sunday, Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me.
During the prayer, he prophesied that a spirit of man entered into me from a young age.
He said that last week, Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for him and prophecied to him,
saying that a spirit of man entered him from a young age.
Marcelo Maldonado - Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
He asked if I was a pastor or a preacher and I replied that yes, I used to be one.
He asked me if I used to preach and I said, "Yes, I used to preach before".
I grew up in a Christian family with uncles who were pastors and evangelists.
At the age of five, a family member abused me.
He said that he grew up in a Christian family. His parents, his uncles were pastors.
When he was five years old, he was raped by a male member of his family.
That was the beginning of emotional and spiritual suffering.
This spirit began to dominate my mind and my emotions with inclination towards the male sex.
He said that from that moment, this spirit entered him and his life became suffering.
He lost any affection for the opposite sex and just began to feel affection for men like him.
At the age of 12, I had my first relationship with a man who was older than me.
When he was 12 years old, he had his first sexual relationship with a man that was older than him.
I felt no affection for the opposite female sex.
He said he didn't feel any affection towards the female sex.
As I grew up with my family in the church, I was preaching and searching for God.
I loved God but there was always a struggle inside me that I had ended up losing.
He said that during this time, he grew up in a church.
He was even trying to preach in the church but he felt so guilty
and there was always a struggle inside of him.
I thought that there was no solution to the problem I was experiencing.
Despite praying, fasting and reading the Bible, I was never able to be free from this spirit.
He said he kept trying to be free from this spirit but he could not.
He read the Bible; he tried to pray; he tried to go to different churches.
There was no solution. He could not receive freedom from this spirit.
I decided to abandon the church and stop praying and reading my Bible.
I started to enter into the world of darkness, going to the night clubs,
joining the occult and taking drugs.
He said that it got to a point where it was so bad that he decided to abandon the church.
He decided to go into the world. He started drinking, taking drugs, going to discos, going to clubs.
In the Law faculty where I was studying, I developed an obsession for a young man.
The obsession was so much that I went to the internet to acquire powers to seduce him.
He said he was studying Law at the university
and there was one boy in his class that he became obsessed with.
In order to seduce him, he decided to go to the internet to get evil powers.
I did a covenant with a spirit called 'Eros' which gave me evil powers
just as Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied that I had evil powers.
It is true. I had power in my eyes, power in my mouth to seduce and in my mind to control.
So just like Prophet T.B. Joshua prophecied that I had evil powers - it is true.
I went to the internet and did a pact, a covenant with a god called 'Eros'.
It is like a god of love.
And he said that after that, he gained powers -
power in his eyes and in his mouth to seduce and in his mind to control.
Once in the bus coming back from university, I saw a man that I liked
and with just one look, I seduced him and he gave me his number.
Prophecy and Deliverance Testimony
He said that these powers gave him that ability to seduce men.
And as soon as he started using them, men would follow him and
he would initiate them and sleep with them.
Let me ask my friend: How are you feeling now after the prayer on last Sunday?
Can you share your experience after that prayer on Sunday. What followed?
When the Prophet called me and said I should stand up,
I automatically felt as if my feet were not on the ground.
The Prophet said I should come and I can't remember everything that happened
but I felt like an electric shock in my body and my stomach turned upside down.
He said that when the Prophet prayed for him, he felt as if he was walking on the air.
His feet were not on the ground.
He felt like an electric shock came through his body.
After the prayer of the Prophet, I felt like a huge burden was lifted from me.
A bondage of years was removed forever.
He said that after the prayer, this spirit has left him forever.
The feeling, urge towards men and all other - he should tell us what happened to them after the prayer.
Marcelo Maldonado - Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
After the man of God prayed for me, it is strange but I look at women and find them beautiful.
He said that after the prayer, now he doesn't feel that affection for men.
Now when he sees women, he can appreciate that they are beautiful.
Hm ... hm.
Wait ... wait.
Marcelo Maldonado - Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
He said that he appreciates women now and now he sees a man as a man.
Does he mean that there is no urge towards men again?
Marcelo Maldonado - Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
Before, it was normal for me to have affection for men
but when I discovered Prophet T.B. Joshua on YouTube, I realised that it was an evil spirit.
Marcelo Maldonado - Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
He said that after the prayer, now he can see a man and
he doesn't feel that attraction towards them like before.
He said that he discovered Prophet T.B. Joshua on YouTube
and that's when he realised that this spirit was actually an evil spirit.
It wasn't normal to feel that attraction for men.
Now, I don't feel any affection for the male sex. I am not attracted to them at all.
He said that now he can look at men and he doesn't have any attraction.
He doesn't feel any sexual attraction towards them at all.
But seeing women - how do you appreciate women now?
Marcelo Maldonado - Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
Now, I look at women and see them as beautiful.
He said that when he sees women now, he can see that they are beautiful
and he can appreciate them that they are really pretty and beautiful now.
Anywhere you are, women, clap for Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Well, this is Jesus for you.
Can you just give your advice to the world. What advice do you have for the whole world?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Marcelo Maldonado - Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
This is a spiritual problem and requires a spiritual solution.
I pray that my testimony reaches those who are struggling with what I struggled with.
It is not normal; it is spiritual and spiritual problems are only solved by the Spirit.
He said that his advice is that this problem is a spiritual problem.
Therefore, it needs a spiritual solution.
The people that are suffering from this same spirit that he had -
the answer for them is to receive a spiritual solution which is deliverance.
Clap for Jesus Christ.
Marcelo Maldonado - Prophecy & Deliverance Testimony
So now, you are free. You are completely free within and outside you.
Amen! Yes, I am totally free, in the name of Jesus!
He said: "Yes, I am totally free, in the name of Jesus!"
Thank you, Lord.
Give thanks to God!
Waive your hand and say, "Thank you, Lord!"